https://dgr.com/privacy-statement-3/

Skip to content
Privacy Statement
DGR Engineering recognizes your right to privacy, and is committed to protecting the privacy interests of visitors to this website. This policy summarizes the collection and use of information gathered by DGR Engineering's website, and other relevant privacy issues.
Only personal information voluntarily provided by users of this site is collected. Information will be used for internal DGR Engineering purposes only and will not be sold to third parties. Non-identifiable technical information, such as the type of browser or operating system used and user domain name, may be automatically collected. This information enables DGR Engineering to measure and improve site usage.
Our web site may contain links to sites of other organizations. DGR Engineering is not responsible for the content of any of those sites and cannot guarantee that they maintain the same privacy standards. Please refer to the privacy policies of those sites.
DGR Engineering does not collect any personal information from children under the age of 18. Children under 18 should not submit personal information without the consent and guidance of a parent or legal guardian.
If you have any questions about DGR Engineering's privacy policy, or would like any personal information you have submitted through this site to be modified or removed, please submit your request on our Contact Us page.
DGR Engineering reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Updates or modifications will be posted to this page.
Bidding DocumentsAviationCivilElectrical PowerSurveyWastewaterWaterAbout UsLocationsNews and EventsCareersContactOur WorkFacebookTwitterLinkedIn
